Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers, 1952-1973
Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers,
1952-1973
61
3 boxes (1.0 linear ft.)
University of California, Los Angeles. Library. Performing Arts Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Tony Barrett was a talented writer and producer who contributed to a variety of radio, television, and motion pictures projects. Among those projects were: The Mod Squad, Burke's Law, Felony Squad, Peter Gunn, and the Snoop Sisters. The collection consists of script and production material related to his career.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Advance notice required for access.
Biography
Tony Barrett was born May 24, 1916 in NY, New York. He was married to writer Steffi Barrett. The multi-talented Barrett was a radio and screen actor, screenwriter and television writer and producer. Among his numerous credits are The Mod Squad, Burke's Law, Felony Squad, Peter Gunn, and the Snoop Sisters. He died of cancer in Los Angeles, CA, November 16, 1974.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of material related to the career of producer and writer, Tony Barrett. Includes scripts, production material, notes, and correspondence. Contains material for approximately 80 television series, 20 radio programs, and 10 motion pictures and teleplays including The Mod Squad (1968-73), Burke's Law (1963-6), Felony Squad (1966-7), Peter Gunn (1958-61), and Snoop Sisters (1973). Also includes bound volumes of scripts.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Scripts (documents).; Radio writers--Archival resources.; Barrett, Tony,--1916-1974--Archives.; Television producers and directors--Archival resources.; Television writers--Archival resources.
Container List
The following online container list has not yet been edited.
- Mod Squad
  - .. AND A LITTLE CHILD SHALL BLEED THEM, 6/14/1971., 21; BARRETT, TONY
  - .. AND A LITTLE CHILD SHALL BLEED THEM, 6/14/1971., 21; BARRETT, STEFFI and BARRETT, TONY
  - 'A' IS FOR ANNIE, 6/17/1970., 14; BAST, WILLIAM
  - ACTIVIST, THE, 8/17/1970., 16; RUBIN, MANN
  - AND ONCE FOR MY BABY, 11/14/1972., 32; SHERMAN, ROBERT
  - ANOTHER FINAL GAME, 7/28/1972., 28; TELFORD, FRANK
  - BAD MAN ON CAMPUS, 6/17/1968., 2; HEVERLY, ROBERT
  - BELINDA - THE END OF LITTLE MISS BUBBLE GUM!, 9/12/1972., 30; MORGAN, BRYN
  - BIG GEORGE, 1/4/1972., 25; LANDAU, RICHARD
  - BUMMER FOR R.J., A, 10/28/1970., 18; TURLEY, JACK
  - CALL BACK YESTERDAY, 1/22/1970., 13; BLOCH, JOHN W. and BLOCH, JOHN W. (STORY)
  - CALL BACK YESTERDAY, 1/22/1970., 13; BLOCH, JOHN W. (STORY) and BLOCH, JOHN W.
  - CALL BACK YESTERDAY, 1/22/1970., 13; YOUNG, ROBERT MALCOLM and BLOCH, JOHN W. and BLOCH, JOHN W. (STORY)
  - CAN YOU HEAR ME OUT THERE, 8/3/1972., 29; ROSS, STANLEY RALPH
  - CAPTAIN GREER CALL SURGERY, 7/9/1968., 2; LAWRENCE, TONY
  - CAVE, THE, 12/3/1971., 25; INGALLS, DON
  - CHILD OF A CHILD, 10/23/1972., 31; (?), MARGARET and SCHNEIDER, PAUL
  - CHILD OF A CHILD, 10/23/1972., 31; SCHNEIDER, PAUL
  - CHILD OF SORROW, CHILD OF LIGHT, 1/8/1969., 6; GOULD, CLIFF
  - COLOR OF LAUGHTER, COLOR OF TEARS, 5/5/1971., 20; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - COMEBACK, THE, 12/28/1970., 19; RUBIN, MANN
  - CONFRONTATION!, 7/11/1969., 9; BELLAK, GEORGE
  - CONNECTION, THE, 5/4/1972., 26; HUSKY, RICK
  - CONNECTION, THE, 5/4/1972., 26; HUSKY, RICK
  - CORBEY, 8/17/1972., 29; TURLEY, JACK
  - CRICKET, 7/28/1971., 22; HUSKY, RICK
  - CRIME CLUB, 7/24/1972., 29; FLICKER, THEODORE J.
  - CRY UNCLE, 12/22/1972., 33; STERN, SANDOR
  - DEADLY SIN, THE, 12/22/1969., 12; YOUNG, ROBERT MALCOLM
  - DEAL WITH THE DEVIL, 10/25/1971., 24; DENNIS, ROBERT C.
  - DEATH IN HIGH PLACES, 11/29/1972., 32; HAMNER, ROBERT
  - DEATH OF A NOBODY, 8/27/1971., 22; RUBIN, MANN
  - DEATH OF WILD BILL HANNACHEK, THE, 8/22/1969., 9; SAHA, MARK
  - DEBT, THE, 11/20/1969., 11; BARRETT, TONY
  - DEBT, THE, 11/20/1969., 11; STEFFI and BARRETT, TONY
  - DOUBLE FOR DANGER, A, 11/11/1970., 18; LEWIS, ROGER HILL
  - EXILE, THE, 11/28/1969., 11; BENNETT, HARVE
  - EXILE, THE, 11/28/1969., 11; RICHMAN, DON and BENNETT, HARVE
  - EXIT THE CLOSER, 7/10/1971., 21; COLLINS, ROBERT
  - EYE FOR AN EYE, AN, 6/3/1969., 8; BARRETT, TONY
  - EYES OF THE BEHOLDERS, 5/31/1972., 26; STEFFI and BARRETT, TONY
  - EYES OF THE BEHOLDERS, 5/31/1972., 26; BARRETT, TONY
  - FAR AWAY PLACE SO NEAR, A, 7/3/1970., 15; APSTEIN, THEODORE
  - FEAR IS THE BUCKING HORSE, 11/19/1968., 5; BARRETT, TONY
  - FEET OF CLAY, 10/4/1971., 23; INGALLS, DON
  - FEVER, 9/22/1970., 17; SCHNEIDER, PAUL
  - FEVER, 9/22/1970., 17; MARGARET and SCHNEIDER, PAUL
  - FIND TARA CHAPMAN!, 8/21/1968., 3; SANFORD, GERALD
  - FIND TARA CHAPMAN!, 8/21/1968., 3; WEINGARTEN, ART and SANFORD, GERALD
  - FLIGHT FIVE DOESN'T ANSWER, 11/13/1968., 5; BENNETT, HARVE (TELEPLAY) and KANDEL, STEPHEN (STORY)
  - FLIGHT FIVE DOESN'T ANSWER, 11/13/1968., 5; KANDEL, STEPHEN (STORY)
  - FUR COAT OF DEATH,THE, 7/10/1972., 28; SANFORD, GERALD
  - GIRL IN CHAIR NINE, THE, 5/19/1969., 7; BAST, WILLIAM
  - GIRL'S BEST FRIEND, A, 10/23/1968., 4; BAGNI, GWEN and DUBOV, PAUL
  - GIRL'S BEST FRIEND, A, 10/23/1968., 4; DUBOV, PAUL
  - GOOD TIMES ARE JUST MEMORIES, 5/10/1972., 28; STERN, SANDOR (TELEPLAY) and BLUELL, RICHARD (STORY)
  - GOOD TIMES ARE JUST MEMORIES, 5/10/1972., 28; BLUELL, RICHARD (STORY) and STERN, SANDOR (TELEPLAY)
  - GOOD TIMES ARE JUST MEMORIES, 5/10/1972., 28; SCHWEITZER, S. (TELEPLAY) and STERN, SANDOR (TELEPLAY) and BLUELL, RICHARD (STORY)
  - GUESS WHO'S COMING TO MURDER, 5/6/1968., 2; ROSS, JEROME
  - GURU, THE, 5/6/1968., 1; CHAPMAN, LEIGH
  - HEALER, THE, 7/31/1969., 9; BAGNI, GWEN and DUBOV, PAUL
  - HEALER, THE, 7/31/1969., 9; DUBOV, PAUL
  - HINT OF DARKNESS, A HINT OF LIGHT, A, 1/2/1969., 6; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - HOT HOT CAR, THE, 11/20/1970., 18; SCHWARTZ, ELROY
  - I AM MY BROTHER'S KEEPER, 10/7/1971., 23; SCHMERER, JAMES
  - IN THIS CORNER -- SOL ALPERT, 9/25/1969., 10; LAKIN, RITA and BENNETT, HARVE
  - IN THIS CORNER -- SOL ALPERT, 9/25/1969., 10; BENNETT, HARVE
  - IS THAT JUSTICE?, 12/9/1970., 18; VOWELL, DAVID H.
  - IS THERE ANYONE LEFT IN SANTA PAULA?, 10/15/1970., 17; COON, GENE L.
  - JIGSAW, 8/31/1971., 23; HUSKY, RICK
  - JUDAS TRAP, THE, 10/2/1970., 17; BLACK, WALTER (TELEPLAY) and BLACK, WALTER (STORY) and BORETZ, ALVIN (STORY)
  - JUDAS TRAP, THE, 10/2/1970., 17; BLACK, WALTER (STORY) and BORETZ, ALVIN (STORY)
  - JUDAS TRAP, THE, 10/2/1970., 17; BORETZ, ALVIN (STORY) and BLACK, WALTER (STORY)
  - JUST RING THE BELL TWICE, 4/6/1970., 16; BAGNI, GWEN and DUBVO, PAUL
  - JUST RING THE BELL TWICE, 4/6/1970., 16; DUBVO, PAUL
  - KEEP THE FAITH, BABY, 2/10/1969., 6; BENNETT, HARVE
  - KICKS, INCORPORATED, 10/25/1970., 17; O'SHEA, PEGGY
  - KILL GENTLY, SWEET JESSIE, 10/26/1971., 24; BARRETT, TONY
  - KILL GENTLY, SWEET JESSIE, 10/26/1971., 24; BARRETT, STEFFI and BARRETT, TONY
  - KING OF EMPTY CUPS, THE, 10/28/1969., 11; ROBERTS, SONYA
  - KRISTIE, 10/4/1972., 30; HUSKY, RICK
  - LISA, 8/14/1969., 9; BARRETT, TONY
  - LISA, 8/14/1969., 9; STEFFI and BARRETT, TONY
  - LONG ROAD HOME, THE, 5/13/1970., 14; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - LOSER, THE, 2/16/1970., 13; STARK, SHELDON
  - LOSER, THE, 6/2/1971., 23; DENNIS, ROBERT C.
  - LOVE, 9/3/1968., 4; ROSENBAUM, HENRY
  - MEDICINE MEN, THE, 5/20/1971., 21; WEINGARTEN, ARTHUR
  - MOTHER OF SORROW, 12/18/1969., 12; LAKIN, RITA (TELEPLAY)
  - MOTHER OF SORROW, 12/18/1969., 12; WOOD, WILLIAM (STORY) and LAKIN, RITA (TELEPLAY)
  - MY NAME IS MANOLETE, 6/10/1969., 8; ARMEN, MARGARET
  - MY, WHAT A PRETTY BUS, 5/28/1968., 1; DUBOV, PAUL
  - MY, WHAT A PRETTY BUS, 5/28/1968., 1; BAGNI, GWEN and DUBOV, PAUL
  - NEVER GIVE THE FUZZ AN EVEN BREAK, 9/11/1969., 10; WALD, MALVIN
  - NIGHT HOLDS TERROR, THE, 12/20/1972., 33; HUSKY, RICK
  - NO MORE OAK LEAVES FOR ERNIE HOLLAND, 11/18/1971., 24; WEINGARTEN, ARTHUR
  - OUTSIDE POSITION, 11/17/1971., 25; SCHWEITZER, S. S.
  - PEACE NOW -- ARLY BLAU!, 2/26/1969., 7; WOOD, WILLIAM
  - PIGEON WITH A BROKEN WING, 6/4/1971., 20; SCHWEITZER, S. S.
  - PLACE TO RUN, A HEART TO HIDE IN, A, 5/19/1969., 8; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - PLIGHT UPON THE LAND, A, 9/2/1969., 10; LANDAU, RICHARD
  - POISONED MIND, THE, 8/19/1971., 22; FRANKEL, ERNIE
  - PRICE OF LOVE, THE, 1/28/1971., 19; FOSTER, ROBERT
  - PRICE OF LOVE, THE, 1/28/1971., 19; BARRETT, TONY and FOSTER, ROBERT
  - PRICE OF TERROR, THE, 8/13/1968., 3; BARRETT, TONY
  - PUT OUT THE WELCOME MAT FOR DEATH, 11/2/1972., 31; SCHWARTZ, ELROY
  - QUIET WEEKEND IN THE COUNTRY, A, 9/13/1968., 4; BARRETT, TONY (TELEPLAY) and GILLIS, JACKSON (STORY)
  - QUIET WEEKEND IN THE COUNTRY, A, 9/13/1968., 4; GILLIS, JACKSON (STORY)
  - REIGN OF GUNS, A, 12/17/1968., 5; ULLMAN, DAN (STORY)
  - REIGN OF GUNS, A, 12/17/1968., 5; BARRETT, TONY (TELEPLAY) and ULLMAN, DAN (STORY)
  - RETURN TO DARKNESS, RETURN TO LIGHT, 1/18/1970., 13; BENNETT, HARVE
  - RETURN TO DARKNESS, RETURN TO LIGHT, 1/18/1970., 13; LAKSO, EDWARD J. and BENNETT, HARVE
  - RIDE THE MAN DOWN, 5/15/1969., 7; LAKSO, EDWARD J. and BENNETT, HARVE
  - RIDE THE MAN DOWN, 5/15/1969., 7; BENNETT, HARVE
  - RUN FOR THE MONEY, A, 1/21/1969., 6; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - RUN, LINCOLN, RUN!, 10/18/1972., 31; STEWART, DONALD
  - SANCTUARY, 6/12/1972., 27; HAMMER, ROBERT
  - SANDS OF ANGER, THE, 4/6/1971., 20; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - SCION OF DEATH, 11/9/1972., 32; WEBSTER, SKIP
  - SEARCH AND DESTROY, 5/22/1970., 14; HARMON, DAVID P.
  - SEAT BY THE WINDOW, A, 2/11/1969., 7; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - SEE THE EAGLES DYING, 5/12/1970., 15; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - SENTINELS, THE, 5/21/1971., 21; BORETZ, ALVIN
  - SHELLGAME, 11/25/1968., 5; LAKSO, EDQARD J.
  - SHOCKWAVE, 11/11/1971., 24; HUSKY, RICK
  - SHOULD AULD ACQUAINTANCE BE FORGOT, 2/8/1970., 13; HAMMIL, JOEL (STORY) and LAKSO, EDWARD J. (STORY) and LAKIN, RITA (TELEPLAY)
  - SHOULD AULD ACQUAINTANCE BE FORGOT, 2/8/1970., 13; LAKIN, RITA (TELEPLAY) and LAKSO, EDWARD J. (STORY)
  - SHOULD AULD ACQUAINTANCE BE FORGOT, 2/8/1970., 13; LAKSO, EDWARD J. (STORY) and LAKIN, RITA (TELEPLAY)
  - SONG OF WILLIE, THE, 7/23/1970., 15; BARRETT, STEFFI and BARRETT, TONY
  - SONG OF WILLIE, THE, 7/23/1970., 15; BARRETT, TONY
  - SUFFER, LITTLE CHILDREN, 8/24/1970., 16; COON, GENE L.
  - SUNDAY DRIVERS, THE, 10/21/1968., 4; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - SURVIVAL, 5/14/1971., 20; BLACK, WALTER (TELEPLAY) and SCHWARTZ, ELROY (STORY) and BLACK, WALTER (STORY)
  - SURVIVAL, 5/14/1971., 20; BLACK, WALTER (STORY) and SCHWARTZ, ELROY (STORY)
  - SURVIVAL, 5/14/1971., 20; SCHWARTZ, ELROY (STORY) and BLACK, WALTER (STORY)
  - SURVIVAL HOUSE, 12/10/1969., 12; BENNETT, HARVE
  - SWEET CHILD OF TERROR, 10/16/1969., 10; LAKSO, EDWARD J.
  - TANGLED WEB, THE, 12/21/1971., 25; FRANKEL, ERNEST
  - TAPS. PLAY IT LOUDER, 6/20/1972., 27; STERN, SANDOR
  - TEETH OF THE BARRACUDA, THE, 10/24/1967., 1; BARRETT, TONY and RUSKIN, BUDDY(CREATED BY)
  - TEETH OF THE BARRACUDA, THE, 10/24/1967., 1; RUSKIN, BUDDY(CREATED BY)
  - THUNDER MAKERS, THE, 4/20/1972., 26; TURLEY, JACK
  - TIME FOR REMEMBERING, A, 1/12/1970., 12; BENNETT, HARVE
  - TIME OF HYACINTHS, A, 9/9/1970., 16; ARMEN, MARGARET
  - TIME TO LOVE -- A TIME TO CRY, A, 8/2/1968., 3; KANDEL, STEPHEN
  - TO LINC -- WITH LOVE, 7/3/1969., 8; SOBIESKI, CAROL
  - TOWN CALLED SINCERE, A, 11/11/1969., 11; DUBOV, PAUL
  - TOWN CALLED SINCERE, A, 11/11/1969., 11; BAGNI, GWEN and DUBOV, PAUL
  - TWAIN, THE, 9/28/1972., 30; WEBSTER, SKIP
  - UP TIGHT TOWN, THE, 5/13/1968., 1; KATKOV, NORMAN
  - WE SPY, 1/23/1971., 19; BLACK, WALTER and BENNETT, HARVE
  - WE SPY, 1/23/1971., 19; BENNETT, HARVE
  - WELCOME TO OUR CITY, 1/8/1971., 19; BARRETT, TONY (TELEPLAY) and HENDRYX, SHIRL (STORY)
  - WELCOME TO OUR CITY, 1/8/1971., 19; HENDRYX, SHIRL (TELEPLAY) and BARRETT, TONY (TELEPLAY) and HENDRYX, SHIRL (STORY)
  - WELCOME TO OUR CITY, 1/8/1971., 19; HENDRYX, SHIRL (STORY) and BARRETT, TONY (TELEPLAY)
  - WELCOME TO THE HUMAN RACE, LEVI FRAZEE!, 6/5/1970., 15; BLACK, WALTER
  - WHEN SMITTY COMES MARCHING HOME, 7/15/1968., 2; BARRETT, TONY and BENNETT, HARVE
  - WHEN SMITTY COMES MARCHING HOME, 7/15/1968., 2; BENNETT, HARVE
  - WHO ARE THE KEEPERS, WHO ARE THE INMATES?, 6/2/1970., 14; LANDAU, RICHARD
  - WILD WEEK-END, 8/6/1971., 22; TURLEY, JACK
  - YESTERDAY'S ASHES, 6/30/1972., 27; WEBSTER, SKIP
  - YOU CAN'T TELL THE PLAYERS WITHOUT A PROGRAMMER, 7/29/1968., 3; BENNETT, HARVE
  - YOU CAN'T TELL THE PLAYERS WITHOUT A PROGRAMMER, 7/29/1968., 3; BARRETT, TONY and BENNETT, HARVE